https://dtidatarecovery.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Request Help
We are happy to help! Please fill out this form or call us Call: 866-438-6932
Name*CompanyEmail*
Phone*Device*Hard DriveRAIDServerSD CardThumb DriveTabletPhoneOtherMedia Size*0GB - 1TB1.5TB - 2TB3TB and upProblem
New York
Why Choose DTI Data Recovery?
Data Recovery Price Match Guarantee
In The News
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
In accordance with our privacy policy, DTI Data collects information from you when you fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
To process transactions.
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the security of your personal information when you place an order, enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your web browser that enables the site or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted here.
This policy was last modified on 11-6-2017
Name*CompanyPhone*Email*
Device*Hard DriveRAIDServerSD CardThumb DriveTabletPhoneOtherMedia Size*0GB - 1TB1.5TB - 2TB3TB and upProblem
Data Recovery company, DTI Data Recovery since 1998.
stts: Here you go, I have one of those Toshiba MK4019GAX...
Rocks: Hello John,
Nice article and thanks for that.
...
Moe: Hi to all, the contents present at this site are r...
Kevin K: Hello. I\'m trying to recover data from a SSD that...
jcooper: Thanks for making this very easy to understand...
Contact Us: 6643 1st Ave S, St.Petersburg, FL, 33707 727-345-9665
© 2020 DTI Data Recovery. All Rights Reserved.
Contact Us
We are happy to help! Please fill out this form or call us Call: 866-438-6932
Name*CompanyEmail*
Phone*Device*Hard DriveRAIDServerSD CardThumb DriveTabletPhoneOtherMedia Size*0GB - 1TB1.5TB - 2TB3TB and upProblem
//www.googleadservices.com/pagead/conversion.js
